

jtluns9@yahoo.com | 9256731600 | Napa, CA 94558

Summary

Jacob is a graduate of the University of Denver with a degree in business administration in marketing and former Division-I student athlete. For the past 3 years Jacob has worked as a Residential Solar Panel Advisor. He is known to be a meticulous hard worker by his coworkers and employers. After working several years in sales Jacob decided to switch things up and began learning to code more in depth using many freely available resources online such as freeCodeCamp, Harvard's CS50 program, and countless other tutorials on Youtube. Jacob has primarily focused on the programming language Python.

Skills

- Friendly, Positive Attitude
- Problem Resolution
- Planning & Organizing
- Critical Thinking

- Computer Skills
- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Programming Languages: JavaScript, Python, CSS/HTML, Django, SQL
- Source and Version Control: Git, Github

Experience

HomePro Solutions | Brentwood, CA **Solar Advisor**

01/2020 - Current

- Developed expertise in renewable energy and smart home products to better serve customers' needs and promote products.
- Prepared proposals, quotes, contracts and presentations for solar customer review.
- Promoted high customer satisfaction by resolving problems with knowledgeable and friendly service.

Excel in Basketball | Concord, CA **Basketball Coach** 06/2011 - 07/2019

- Motivated and encouraged student athletes to make best effort during practices and games.
- Assessed player abilities and assigned positions according to individual strengths.
- Ran drills and fitness circuits to improve athletes' coordination and skills.

Education and Training

University of Denver | Denver, CO **Bachelor of Arts** in Business Administration 06/2018

- 2015-2018 Dean's List
- Guard for DU Men's Basketball, 2015 to 2017
- Completed CS50/CS50W/CS50P Course
- Completed freeCodeCamp Course
- Sweden Studies Abroad on Biblical Theology
- Guatemala Studies Abroad on Spanish

Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

- Jalu589.pythonanywhere.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/jacob-lunsford-27530a138/
- https://github.com/jalu589